<resources>
    <string name="play">PLAY</string>
    <string name="options">Options</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="start">Start</string>
    <string name="points">Points: %1$s</string>
    <string name="left">left: %1$s</string>
    <string name="round">Round: %1$s</string>
    <string name="wrath_of_fortune_plus_one"> +1 </string>
    <string name="restore_time">time restore: -0.1</string>
    <string name="home">HOME</string>
    <string name="restart">RESTART</string>
    <string name="music">Music</string>
    <string name="sound">Sound</string>
    <string name="on">On</string>
    <string name="off">Off</string>
    <string name="skills">Skills</string>
    <string name="label_wrath_of_fortune">Wrath of Fortune</string>
    <string name="enemy">Enemy</string>
    <string name="shop">Shop</string>
    <string name="enemy_minotaur">Minotaur</string>
    <string name="enemy_meduza">Medusa Gorgon</string>
    <string name="enemy_hydra">Hydra</string>
    <string name="start_wave">Start wave</string>
    <string name="skill_thunder">Thunder</string>
    <string name="skill_windstorm">Windstorm</string>
    <string name="skill_earthquake">Earthquake</string>
    <string name="about_description">Long ago, Olympus was an impregnable fortress of the gods, where peace and harmony reigned. But one day the depths of Tartarus released the most terrible creatures: the Minotaur, Medusa the Gorgon and the many-headed Hydra. Their goal is to destroy the sacred gates of Olympus and overthrow Zeus, the chief protector of the gods.</string>
    <string name="minotaur_description">Minotaur
Description: A huge, strong creature with the body of a man and the head of a bull. The Minotaur is the easiest enemy in the game.
Mechanics: One hit is enough to destroy.
Features: Fast</string>
    <string name="meduza_description">Medusa Gorgon
Description: A terrifying woman with snakes instead of hair. Her gaze hides a magical power that makes everyone who sees her freeze.
Mechanics: Requires two hits to destroy.
Features: The fastest.</string>
    <string name="hydra_description">Hydra
Description: A multi-headed serpent, a legendary creature that will test your agility and reaction.
Mechanics: Requires three hits to destroy.
Features: The strongest and slowest enemy. The more Hydra appears, the harder it is to avoid damage.</string>
    <string name="skill_thunder_description">Zeus releases lightning at all visible enemies, thereby destroying them.</string>
    <string name="skill_windstorm_description">Zeus summons a storm that creates a strong gust of wind and hinders enemies from advancing.</string>
    <string name="skill_earthquake_description">From the power of Zeus, the very earth trembles and the enemies turn to flee.
Takes a small amount of damage.</string>
    <string name="skill_wrath_of_fortune_description">Gives you the ability to use one of your abilities even when it is on cooldown, or gives you extra points. Fortune doesn't always smile on Zeus.</string>
</resources>

